Ted scores again!
Oh my gosh!
Ted just slipped
right through
that tackle like
it was nothing!
Ted Vincent
is looking
like a superhero!
He just cut through
our entire defense!
God,
he's worth at least
a hundred million
on the
open market.
What? A
hundred million?
At least.
You called him a
washed-up nobody?
You had a star
on the team
and you cut him.
I don't know
how he's doing this.
He was a scrub that
we had
doing odd jobs.
I... I... I don't...
He's not supposed
to be good.
You idiot! You
let this talent walk!
West must go!
Boo...
This mess
is on you, West!
I should have never
listened to you.
There's no way I
can lose this game.
If we lose, I'm out.
I can't afford to
lose everything.
Garcia!
Let's see how
you like this, Ted.